# **Cyncere Howard**

Preferred Name: Cy Howard W232 N91675 Wooded Ridge Trail Sussex, WI 53089 (262) 422-4357 cyhoward47@gmail.com

## Skills

I have over five years of customer service/sales experience, with over two years of insurance experience. I have experience with handling high volume inbound calls, assisting clients/agents, claims handling, and underwriting. I have experience managing people and a store, as well as over two years of training experience. I enjoy meeting new people and being able to bring a positive attitude to every conversation I have.

## Certifications

- Property and Casualty Insurance License (Expires August 2021)
- Microsoft Office Certification in Word, Excel, and Powerpoint (Achieved in 2017)

# **Experience**

July 2018 - August 2020

#### Markel American Insurance, Pewaukee, WI - Marine Specialist

- I was responsible for helping inquiring clients with insurance, from quote to binding. I also assisted existing clients with amending their current insurance, updating their profile, taking claims, and helping with online account lockouts/issues.
- With the position of marine specialist I had the added responsibility of helping to train new employees in watercraft insurance, assisting underwriting, attending underwriting meetings, helping other employees with quoting/product questions. After the months of training with underwriting, I was given authority to fully underwrite certain risks.
- I would take inbound calls/emails from agents nationwide to process their applications and if it was within my authority to underwrite the risk.
- Using Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, and OneNote to help with daily tasks.

August 2017 - July 2018

#### MarketSource, Chicago, IL - Sales Associate and Trainer

- I was in charge of all HP related products at select Best Buy and Office Depot stores.
- I was responsible for training the store employees on HP products, answering product related questions, in person selling at the stores, reporting of sales, and solving in store issues related to HP products.

- I was responsible for the store's sales numbers, displays, and products. I would have to actively think and implement plans to improve the numbers/techniques of the store.
- The store I was working at was ranked eighth in Chicago in sales, and within 2 months I got the store to being ranked first and kept that position for the rest of my duration working there.

October 2015 - August 2017

#### Best Buy, Menomonee Falls, WI - Sales Associate

- My responsibilities included stocking products, assisting customers, answering product related questions, and selling the product.
- My duties consisted of lifting computers and printers up and down ladders in order to stock them and find the perfect solution that fits the needs and wants of each customer.

August 2015 - October 2015

#### Culver's, Sussex, WI - Crew Member

- I was responsible for maintaining customer satisfaction.
- My duties included taking customers orders, preparing food, and cleaning the restaurant.

## **Education**

September 2013- 2017

Sussex Hamilton High School, Sussex, WI - 2017

University of Illinois at Chicago - Computer Science - 2017-2018, Withdrew

## **Awards**

Top selling employee for the computers department for Best Buy store 757 in November 2015, December 2015, February 2016. Highest NPS(survey score) for the year of 2016 in the Best Buy 757 store. Highest premium bound Jan 2020-August 2020 at Markel.